neucopia.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Neucopia

**Privacy Policy**

Neucopia is committed to customer service and we intend to uphold this by providing a private and secure browsing experience. The following policy will help you to understand how we will treat your personal information. As we continue to improve our site and as we take advantage of developments in technology, this policy may change from time to time so please check this policy on an ongoing basis for revisions and updates.

**Information Collection and Use**

Neucopia collects information from our web site in several ways. During registration, Neucopia asks for information such as your name, phone number, and email address. Once you have submitted this information and chosen a valid password, you will be able to take full advantage of everything Neucopia has to offer. You may also be asked for personal information when you report a problem with our site, or services; or, if you otherwise contact Neucopia. Neucopia also collects information using cookies, which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. This information allows us to automatically link our customers to their personalized accounts. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Please check your browser’s guidelines should you wish to prevent cookies. Neucopia is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, rent or otherwise distribute this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Information is collected with the sole purpose of providing Neucopia products and customer service.

**Information Disclosure**

When you are on the Neucopia site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with only Neucopia, its agents and representatives. Neucopia will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. Neucopia may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Neucopia’s rights or property, other Neucopia users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Neucopia will comply with the requests of all recognized legal entities to aid in the stopping of spam, distribution of illicit sexual content to minors, or any other illegal activity brought to our attention through such channels.

Neucopia may occasionally send you e-mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only Neucopia (or agents or representatives working on behalf of Neucopia) will send you these emails. You may unsubscribe from the service information updates without any future correspondence or questions by filling out the Opt-Out Form.
